Guide to the American Newspaper Repository Collection, 1852-2004 RL.10057
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1920-1971, 93
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1962 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1231)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1962 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1247)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1963 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1217)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1963 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1159)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1963 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1244)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1963 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1233)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1964 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1595)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1964 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1203)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1964 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1594)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1964 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1597)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1965 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1598)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1965 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1595)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1965 Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 1594)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1965 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1594)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1966 Jan.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1611)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1966 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1706)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1966 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1711)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1966 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 1711)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1966 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1706)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1967 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1312)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1967 Apr.-May; wrapped bundle (Box 1314)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1967 June-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1283)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1967 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1313)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1968 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1282)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1968 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 477)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1968 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1623)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1969 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1285)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1969 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1622)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1969 Sept.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1284)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1970 Jan.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 478)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1970 May-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1605)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1970 Dec.-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1243)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1971 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1602)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1971 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1227)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1971 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1204)
- Temps, 1896-1897, 94
  - Temps, 1896-1897; volume in box (Box 1698)
- The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1926-1933, 95
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1926 Mar.-Apr.; volume (Volume 6738)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1926 May-June; volume (Volume 6782)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1926 July-Aug.; volume (Volume 6781)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1926 Sept.-Oct.; volume (Volume 6785)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1926 Nov.-Dec.; volume (Volume 6784)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1926-1927; volume (Volume 6793)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1927 Jan.-Feb.; volume (Volume 6783)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1927 Mar.-Apr.; volume (Volume 6736)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1927 May-June; volume (Volume 6737)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1927 July-Aug.; volume (Volume 6780)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1927 Sept.-Oct.; volume (Volume 6762)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1927 Nov.-Dec.; volume (Volume 6787)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1927-1928; volume (Volume 6790)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1928 Jan.-Mar. 3; volume (Volume 6775)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1928 Mar.-Apr.; volume (Volume 6788)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1928 May-June; volume (Volume 6779)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1928 July-Aug.; volume (Volume 6778)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1928 Sept.-Oct.; volume (Volume 6772)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1928 Nov.-Dec.; volume (Volume 6773)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1928-1929; volume (Volume 6792)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1929 Jan.-Mar. 3; volume (Volume 6774)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1929 Mar. 4-1930 Mar. 3; volume (Volume 6791)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1929 Mar.-Apr.; volume (Volume 6766)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1929 May-June; volume (Volume 6765)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1929 July-Aug.; volume (Volume 6764)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1929 Sept.-Oct.; volume (Volume 6771)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1929 Nov.-Dec.; volume (Volume 6767)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1930 Jan.-Mar.; volume (Volume 6768)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1930 Mar. 4-1931 Mar. 3; volume (Volume 6794)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1930 Mar.-Apr.; volume (Volume 6776)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1930 May-June; volume (Volume 6777)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1930 July-Aug.; volume (Volume 6763)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1930 Sept.-Oct.; volume (Volume 6740)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1930 Nov.-Dec.; volume (Volume 5709)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1931 Jan.-Mar. 3; volume (Volume 5710)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1931 Mar.-Apr.; volume (Volume 5711)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1931 May-June; volume (Volume 6769)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1931 July-Aug.; volume (Volume 6770)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1931 Sept.-Oct.; volume (Volume 6732)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1931 Nov.-Dec.; volume (Volume 6729)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1932 Jan.-Mar. 3; volume (Volume 6730)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1932 Mar.-1933 Feb.; volume (Volume 6789)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1932 Mar.-Apr.; volume (Volume 6731)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1932 May-June; volume (Volume 6739)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1932 July-Aug.; volume (Volume 6786)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1932 Sept.-Oct.; volume (Volume 6735)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1932 Nov.-Dec.; volume (Volume 6733)
  - The United States Daily (Washington D.C.), 1933 Jan.-Mar.; volume (Volume 6734)
- Transit Journal News (New York), 1936-1942, 96
  - Transit Journal News (New York), 1936 Dec. 14-26; wrapped bundle (Box 140)
  - Transit Journal News (New York), 1937-1938; wrapped bundle (Box 141)
  - Transit Journal News (New York), 1939-1940; wrapped bundle (Box 138)
  - Transit Journal News (New York), 1941-1942; wrapped bundle (Box 139)
- Tygodnik Polski (New York), 1943, 1945-1947, 97
  - Tygodnik Polski (New York), 1943; wrapped bundle (Box 79)
  - Tygodnik Polski (New York), 1945-1947; wrapped bundle (Box 136)
- Ukrainske Narodne Slovo (Pittsburgh), 1965-1973, 98
  - Ukrainske Narodne Slovo (Pittsburgh), 1965 Jan.-1966 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1351)
  - Ukrainske Narodne Slovo (Pittsburgh), 1967 Jan.-1969 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1352)
  - Ukrainske Narodne Slovo (Pittsburgh), 1970 Jan.-1972 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1354)
  - Ukrainske Narodne Slovo (Pittsburgh), 1973; wrapped bundle (Box 1353)
    [Note: Missing Feb. 1, no.3]
- Ukrainske Zhyttia (Chicago), 1956-1973, 99
  - Ukrainske Zhyttia (Chicago), 1956 May-1958; wrapped bundle (Box 1382)
  - Ukrainske Zhyttia (Chicago), 1959-1961; wrapped bundle (Box 1476)
  - Ukrainske Zhyttia (Chicago), 1962-1964; wrapped bundle (Box 1475)
  - Ukrainske Zhyttia (Chicago), 1965-1968; wrapped bundle (Box 1473)
- Ukranian Life Independent Weekly, 1969-1972
  - Ukranian Life Independent Weekly, 1969-1972 (Box 1903)
- Washington Post International (Paris), 1967, 100
  - Washington Post International (Paris), 1967 Jan.; loose newspaper (Box 1637)
  - Washington Post International (Paris), 1967 Mar.; loose newspaper (Box 1641)
  - Washington Post International (Paris), 1967 May; loose newspaper (Box 1639)
- Washington Post Weekly, 1993-1999, 101
  - Washington Post Weekly, 1993; loose newspaper (Box 360-361, 429-431)
  - Washington Post Weekly, 1994; loose newspaper (Box 358-360, 429)
  - Washington Post Weekly, 1995; loose newspaper (Box 358-360, 430)
  - Washington Post Weekly, 1996; loose newspaper (Box 382-385, 430-431)
  - Washington Post Weekly, 1997; loose newspaper (Box 382-385, 431)
  - Washington Post Weekly, 1998; loose newspaper (Box 382-385)
  - Washington Post Weekly, 1999; loose newspaper (Box 382-385)
- Washington Post, 1963, 1968-1969, 1991-1998, 2001, 102
  - Washington Post, 1963; loose newspaper (Box 1871-1872)
  - Washington Post, 1968-1969; loose newspaper (Box 1871-1872)
  - Washington Post, 1991; loose newspaper (Box 1871-1872)
    [Includes reports of the Gulf War.]
  - Washington Post, 1992-1997; loose newspaper (Box 1583-1584, 1871-1872)
    [Includes reports of the Israeli-PLO peace agreement.]
  - Washington Post, 1998; loose newspaper (Box 1532)
  - Washington Post, 2001; loose newspaper (Box 1578)
- Wisconsin Patriot, 1854-1862, 103
  - Wisconsin Patriot, 1854 Sept. 9-1859 June 25; bound volume (Volume 5811)
  - Wisconsin Patriot, 1859 July 2-1861 Dec. 28; bound volume (Volume 5642)
  - Wisconsin Patriot, 1862 Jan. 4-1863 Dec. 19; bound volume (Volume 5641)